[
	{
		"question": "Who won Faux Life Season 1?",
		"answers": ["Miss", "Vi", "Kawaii"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "How did Kawaii Die in Faux Life Season 1?",
		"answers": ["Fall Damage", "Creeper", "Warden"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "What were the names of the gay goats team LAG?",
		"answers": ["Helium and Poptart", "William and Hubert", "William and Helium"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Where did the hobbits build their base?",
		"answers": ["Mountains", "Forest", "Underground"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was apart of NLO?",
		"answers": ["Classic", "Kawaii", "Vi"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Who killed the most salmon in Faux Life season 1?",
		"answers": ["Miss", "Dio", "Vi"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Which two teams teamed up together in Faux Life?",
		"answers": ["NLO and Lag", "Lag and Hobbits", "Hobbits and NLO"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the name of Kharlie’s Dog in Double Trouble?",
		"answers": ["Gumbo", "Mumbo Jumbo", "Dumbo"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Where was Stormi’s Shop located?",
		"answers": ["The Snow", "The Pale Garden", "Dark Oak Forest"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Where was Miss' Shop located?",
		"answers": ["The Snow", "The Pale Garden", "Dark Oak Forest"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Which food item caused Archie’s first death in Double Trouble?",
		"answers": ["Potato", "Carrot", "Sweet Berry"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Who appeared shorter in session 2 and 3 in Double Life?",
		"answers": ["Ayra", "Kharlie", "Melon"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Which member did scorch have to censor the most in Double Trouble?",
		"answers": ["Gucci", "Kharlie", "Kawaii"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "How many red pairs were there before the idea of 4 lives were added in Double Trouble?",
		"answers": ["2", "3", "4"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Which was the first pair to go red? ",
		"answers": ["Melon and Scorch", "Kawaii and Ayra", "Gucci and Kharlie"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Who won Flying high?",
		"answers": ["Dio", "Nuggie", "Gucci"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Who were the last two alive in Flying? ",
		"answers": ["Nuggie and Dio", "Melon and Kawaii", "Kharlie and Scorch"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Which two mobs fought against each other for a task in Secret Life?",
		"answers": ["Warden vs Guardian", "Warden vs Wither", "Wither vs Ender Dragon"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	}
]